So, hopefully, now that you know how to do the frontwards weave, putting it all together into the backwards weave will be a snap.
Let's start by split time circles just like we did before and we're going to try one continuous cycle and then going back to split time circles.
Starting with my right arm.
One whole weave and then back.
So again, each hand gets a chance to be on top.
My wrists are moving under each other as they cross.
Under.
Watch how the writ comes around my hand and under the other one.
This will enable you to do it without your Poi crossing and tangling with one another.
If you get confused, just come back to split time circles and try again, starting with your right hand leading up to your left shoulder and around.
Think of them going under the other one.
Under.
Good job!